export const lightThemecolor = {
    bg: '#ffffff',
    navBg: '#f2f3f4',
    textColor: '#6e6e6e',
    border: '#cccdd1',
    hightlightBlue: '#3971e0',
    hightlightBlack: '#333333',
    filterBorder: '#E0E0E0',
    socialDropdownBg: '#3871E0',
    numQuestion: '#2E03F5',
    numAnswer: '#1A1A9F',
    signs: '#323940',
    undefinedString: '#323941',
    undefinedAnswer: '#81858A',
    stringQuestion: '#9C251D',
    stringAnswer: '#B82618',
    booleanQuestion: '#201293',
    booleanAnswer: '#1A1B9F',
    nullQuestion: '#9D248B',
    nullAnswer: '#808789',
    undefinedQuestion: '#313940',
    arrowCursor: '#497AE9',
    arrowQuestion: '#939394',
    arrowAnswer: '#BAB9BA',
    caretColor: '#000000',
    ioborder: '#F1EFF0',
    errorBg: '#FCF0F0',
    errorText: '#EA3323',
    errorBorder: '#F8D8D7',
    tagColor: '#7E1F7C',
    attrColor: '#8F4A19',
    attrValueColor: '#1A1AA1',
    docType: '#C0C0C0'
};

export const darkThemecolor = {
    bg: '#202124',
    navBg: '#292a2d',
    textColor: '#9ba0a5',
    border: '#4b4c50',
    hightlightBlue: '#000000',
    hightlightBlack: '#e9eaed',
    filterBorder: '#5A5A5A',
    socialDropdownBg: '#2D6198',
    numQuestion: '#B4F5BB',
    numAnswer: '#9581F7',
    signs: '#BFC6CD',
    undefinedString: '#DAD9D8',
    stringQuestion: '#E4905E',
    stringAnswer: '#6BD1C7',
    booleanQuestion: '#B4F5BA',
    booleanAnswer: '#9581F7',
    nullQuestion: '#9680CE',
    nullAnswer: '#81868A',
    undefinedQuestion: '#D9DAD9',
    undefinedAnswer: '#81868A',
    arrowCursor: '#3B5BA3',
    arrowQuestion: '#939394',
    arrowAnswer: '#BABBBA',
    caretColor: '#ffffff',
    ioborder: '#3B3B3A',
    errorBg: '#250201',
    errorText: '#EF8784',
    errorBorder: '#540C06',
    tagColor: '#71ADD2',
    attrColor: '#A1BAD9',
    attrValueColor: '#E59C6F',
    docType: '#C0C0C0'
};
